EFSTATHIOS STIVAROS

efstathios@ntscreative.co.uk · SE10 · 07960016205

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am a hard-working RoR web developer who thrives on challenges, building relationships and learning. Due to the nature of my business and previous experience I am comfortable in various additional roles. I enjoy working in teams, whether leading or participating as part of a group.

SKILLS

Ruby on Rails • HTML5 & CSS3 • Bootstrap, Javascript & jQuery • Git • BDD (RSpec) Leadership & Teamwork • Communicating & Listening • Project Management

PORTFOLIO

http://stivaros.com

EDUCATION

CareerFoundry Web Development

Remote · January 2017 - July 2017

Six month intensive coding bootcamp, with over 400 hours of coding in Ruby on Rails, Javascript, jQuery, HTML5 and CSS3. See portfolio.

West London Academy

Northolt, West London • A Levels
BTEC Business • Computing
Northolt, West London • GCSEs

BTEC Business · Citizenship · DiDA · Double Science · English Lit/Lang · Maths

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Honeypot Group Operations (The Hive London / Barnet Football Club)

The Hive London, Edgware • July 2015 - January 2017

Originally hired as a P/T foundation coach, made F/T as system administrator within a small, cross-trained, team of four. Outgrew this team and promoted into more diverse roles approximately every four months in recognition of my work ethic and adaptability.

System Administrator

Second line support for bespoke inhouse ticketing system software, supporting 75 users across four sites. System was developed to support three additional business types in this time. I wrote roughly 25 development requests with supporting documentation & designs.

Ticketing & Memberships

IT specialist within a four-person team that included ticketing and memberships specialists. Cross-trained to deal with ticketing and memberships enquiries. Promoted to interim manager, leading team of two, overseeing post-season membership renewals. Introduced KPIs to a team that had attracted bad publicity as a result of disorganisation.

Control Oversight (Business Analyst)

Worked in a team of four to convert a business that was owed six-figures by debtors, had not invoiced properly since formation and which actually possessed 40% of the stock it had on file into a profitable business with strict controls and procedures in place.

IT Manager

Provide 1st line support, ensure uptime across all networks, project manage new builds and/or developments across all four sites in conjunction with suppliers. Reduced costs within IT department by identifying and targeting a "bodge" culture. To set standard, produced cabling map for new stand, cutting costs by ensuring efficient delivery.

NTS Creative Ltd

Home-Registered, Remote Locations • March 2012 - Present (Passive 2015 - Present)

Web Consultant / Developer

Small IT and web development business, clients include NPOs, sole traders and SMEs.

Achievements & Skills

Founded from scratch, only accountancy has been outsourced. All other responsibilities are handled in-house. Client services include web design, web hosting, training programmes, tuition, consultation and servicing, with further bespoke solutions available per project. Streamlined workflow ensures timely project delivery and low costs. Profit margins are high, due to aforementioned low costs, as are customer satisfaction and CLV.

HOBBIES

Football

Coaching football, fuelled by an obsession with Football Manager, has been a passion of mine since I turned 18. In July 2015 I passed my Level 2 coaching certificate, a year after completing my Level 1. My coaching career held my second goal which was to coach at a professional football club, something I am proud to say I achieved in the 2015–16 season.

Other Hobbies

Creative Writing • Badminton & Other Sport • Coding & Designing • Reading